// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Who is the father of C language?",
      answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
      options: [
        "Steve Jobs",
        " James Gosling",
        " Dennis Ritchie",
        " Rasmus Lerdorf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
      answer: "int $main;",
      options: [
        "int number;",
        "float rate;",
        "int variable_count;",
        "int $main;"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: " All keywords in C are in ____________",
      answer: "LowerCase letters",
      options: [
        "LowerCase letters",
        "UpperCase letters",
        "CamelCase letters",
        "none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: " Which of the following is true for variable names in C?",
      answer: "Variable names cannot start with a digit",
      options: [
        " They can contain alphanumeric characters as well as special characters",
        "It is not an error to declare a variable to be one of the keywords(like goto, static)",
        "Variable names cannot start with a digit",
        "Variable can be of any length"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: " Which is valid C expression?",
      answer: "int my_num = 100000;",
      options: [
        "int my_num = 100,000;",
        " int my_num = 100000;",
        "  int my num = 1000",
        "int $my_num = 10000;"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following cannot be a variable name in C?",
      answer: "volatile",
      options: [
        "volatile",
        "true",
        "friend",
        "export"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "What is short int in C programming?",
      answer: "Short is the qualifier and int is the basic data type",
      options: [
        "The basic data type of C",
        "Qualifier",
        "Short is the qualifier and int is the basic data type",
        "All of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following declaration is not supported by C language?",
      answer: "String str;",
      options: [
        "String str;",
        " char *str;",
        " float str = 3e2;",
        "Both String str; & float str = 3e2;"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which keyword is used to prevent any changes in the variable within a C program?",
      answer: "const",
      options: [
        "immutable",
        " mutable",
        "const",
        " volatile"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What is the result of logical or relational expression in C?",
      answer: "0 or 1",
      options: [
        "True or False",
        "0 or 1",
        "0 if an expression is false and any positive number if an expression is true",
        "none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
  ];